[{"answer": "Well, as you know, this is something the president as you know, feels really personally deeply about.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "What kind of response to the worst school shooting in American history is that?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Well, I think that is what the president has been saying to both members -- to both parties, and you know, the reality in the senate today is that the overwhelming majority of Democrats support background checks, and all we need is a small minority of Republicans in the United States Senate to join with the 90 percent of Americans to support doing this.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Isn't that what the president should now be doing?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Well, I think I come from the opposite side of the political divide, if you like, being a labor prime minister.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "How would you sum up her tenure?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Look, she took some very difficult decisions and she took decisions that were often extremely unpopular, so you know, even though over here in America, she would be I think admired probably both sides of the divide.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Why was she so divisive?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Well, the fascinating thing because obviously, I grew up in the sense politically with her as the prime minister, very distant figure.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "What was she like in private, Margaret Thatcher?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Look, I think part of the problem is in modern politics particularly, that if you're in power for any length of time, you take difficult decisions.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Are you speaking as somebody who perhaps is in a similar position, a divisive reaction perhaps back home, but oddly popular perhaps in America as she indeed has proven to be today?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "She sure was.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Rudy, she was quite something, wasn't she, Margaret Thatcher?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "First of all, including by me.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Why is that, do you think?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "Can you recognize that in somebody like her who was so consumed by the job and the power?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "UILIANI: Well, I think revitalizing Great Britain.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "What do you think her legacy should be, Rudy?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "First of all, we don't know what's going to happen.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "This is going to be a big failure, isn't it, for President Obama if he can't do better than this?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Well, I think what Cuomo did was he put together a very -- even a stricter gun control approach.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "I mean, should he be doing more of the Cuomo style of campaigning on this?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "I would not only encourage it, I don't understand it.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "So you would encourage Republicans not to filibuster?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Very well, thank you.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "How you doing?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Second only to Churchill, I would say.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Niall Ferguson, as a fellow Brit, where does Margaret Thatcher rank in the pantheon of British prime ministers?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Oh, I would agree with Niall.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "But where does she stand globally, do you think?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "For the most part, not at all.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "Would we be looking at Margaret Thatcher in a different way if she had been a man presiding over that period in Great Britain?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Well, I have been enjoying your show not least because I heard a former editor of \"The Daily Mirror\" and a former Labor prime minister say positive things about Margaret Thatcher.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Was it fair?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Yeah, you can.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "can I disagree with that?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Well, I think we need to do more to help Japan right now and have a new American military strategy.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Is he doing the right kind of things with North Korea?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Well, I really wish there would be.", "docId": "130408pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Niall Ferguson, guns and America, is there ever going to be a significant cultural change in America in relation to guns, do you think?", "qSentId": 461}]